For this to work, what you need is
the power of my stand, the world.
Beyond the powers my stand
shall bestow upon you lies the
path you must travel in order
to find the gates of heaven.
What you will need once on the
path is a trustworthy friend.
Someone capable of controlling
their own selfish desires.
A person who shares no interest
in sex, fame, wealth, or power.
And above all,
they must be someone who chooses the
will of God before the law of humans.
The question remains, will I ever cross
paths with someone like this one day?
Additionally,
you need the souls of more than 36
humans who have committed atrocious sins.
That is because those who have
sinned harbor a strong power within.
Of equal note, there are 14
words you need to keep in mind.
Their significance is vital to this plan,
so I will engrave them onto my stand to
ensure that I never forget them myself.
What is most necessary is courage.
I'm loath to do so, but I must have the
courage to relinquish my stand once.
As it gradually disintegrates,
my stand will take form and absorb
the souls of the 36 sinners,
and will give birth to
something entirely new.
Whatever is born will awaken.
And once these 14 words are
uttered by my trusted friend,
the newborn will express a keen interest.
In this moment, my friend will trust
me as I befriend this new entity.
Lastly, you will need
an appropriate location.
North latitude, 28 degrees, 24 minutes.
West longitude, 80 degrees, 36 minutes.
Go there, and wait patiently
for the next new moon.
That, my friend, is when heaven will come.
Oh, hello there, Father.
Good morning.
Your hair has gotten longer.
How many days since your last visit?
I have no further use for this prison.
The child that was born is
already in my possession.
Now I simply have to wait for
my faded time to go to heaven.
Okay, all right, all right.
I don't wanna fade, let's go!
Come and find a way.
I want me.
I want you to be me.
Break out,
This is really bad.
Like a nightmare.
They've issued a maximum
class security alert.
Everyone here is armed to the teeth.
And the whole place is
crawling with guards.
I shouldn't even stay here another minute.
Hey, Jolene!
Can you hear me at all?
Are you listening?
The priest is no longer on this island.
He's already left the Green Dolphin
Street prison for who knows what.
But he didn't have any belongings,
and I confirmed that he wasn't
carrying a baby anywhere on him.
I've been so bored I
gave myself a belly ring.
Anyway, did you bring the disc with you?
Emporio, do you have it now?
Did you contact the Speedwagon Foundation?
No way I could with such tight security.
But of course I have the disc, Jolene.
I would never leave it
lying around somewhere.
Look, I'm breaking out.
Lead the way. Jolene,
according to the guards,
they think that you're the only one who
survived what happened
in the Punishment Ward.
They can't accuse you yet,
but at the moment you're the only
person they can question about it.
And this area is the most heavily guarded.
Are you saying you want
to escape to my room?
I don't think you get it, Emporio.
I'm talking about the prison.
I'm breaking out of this place.
I can't sit around here and wait anymore.
It's time.
I'm getting off of Green Dolphin Island.
You'll show me the shortcut.
I'll definitely call the Speedwagon
Foundation for you, Jolene.
I'll try my best to get
a hold of them today.
You're missing the big picture, Emporio.
Getting Dad's disc back
was the first step.
But just because we have it
now doesn't mean this is over.
If FF was still with us, they'd
already be hot on that priest's trail.
And now that I've finally
read my father's memories,
I know what the last 20 years mean!
Also, I understand why my father decided
to seal away Dio's stand ability.
Fact is, my old man would
never let that priest get away.
My name is Jolene Keicho.
It's up to me to seal what
that bastard just obtained.
Emporio, do you honestly
plan to stay here forever?
Ultimately, you decide.
But we can leave together.
I don't think you're understanding.
You just don't get it.
No, I do get it.
Give me three minutes and I can
destroy one of these iron bars.
But what about after that?
There's no one else here
who can help you right now.
It's only me.
Hermes and Anastasia are still
in the medical ward recovering,
and they'll be there a while.
Weather is secluding himself
in his cell for some reason,
and won't even come to my room.
I have that covered.
We can go from the Ultra
Security House unit.
The Marsh is that way. Impossible!
Nobody has been able to
escape this prison, not ever!
There were inmates who were punished
severely for even contemplating breaking out.
But anyway,
unless we can stop time like your dad,
we're going to be stuck here and there's
nothing you or I can do about it.
I can't figure out what, but
there's something more to it.
I mean, something way scarier
than the security cameras.
It's almost as if the prison
itself is watching us.
Emporium, when is the next new
moon on the calendar? Wait, Jolene!
Let's wait for the
Speedwagon Foundation first!
I would hate for us to lose the disk.
It took so much time
and trouble to get back.
North 28 degrees, 24 minutes.
West 80 degrees, 36
minutes. Where is that?
I...
I'm sorry, Jolene.
I want to help you, but I can't.
I have a message from Palesnake.
Listen carefully.
This is the end of the line.
And don't even think
about trying to escape.
If you comply,
I'll make sure no one stops you from getting
your father's disc out of this prison.
Well, you've got guts, that's for sure.
You came right out and showed
me your face and stand.
Wanna tell me your name?
I'm Miu Miu.
And you can call my stand Jailhouse Lock.
I'm showing you as a warning.
I'd take it seriously.
So, let me get this straight.
He told you to finish me off?
Well, yes, if you plan on
escaping later, that is.
Escaping later, you say?
No, that ain't my plan.
This is...
It's inside the bars.
I'm warning you again, Jolene
Kujo, so I know you hear me.
Don't touch the iron bars.
The more you think about escaping, the
closer you'll get to a very ugly death.
Is this your ability?
Like this!
You want me to call someone for you?
What's up, Jolene? You okay?
Hey, wait, where am I?
What is this?
Wait, you're Gwess.
This is the female ward?
Ouch!
One, grab a pen immediately.
Huh?
Two, know that you can only retain
up to three new things at a time.
Three, defeat the stand user.
Her name is Miu Miu.
What's all this?
And who wrote it?
Did they use this pen to write it
all down on me while I was sleeping?
That's it, I remember now.
I was in solitary because
of the security incident.
I pierced my belly button,
and then I saw Emporium.
I told him that I was going to be
escaping so I could go after the priest.
and then after that after that
i and and after i said i was
escaping right somebody showed
up but who what i wrote all these
this is my handwriting that's
impossible when i have no memory
of this hey you why am i suddenly
back here at the female ward.
Hey, answer the question.
Why the hell are you ignoring me?
I've been asleep till now,
so I honestly don't know.
I'm asking you for real.
Okay, okay. That's better.
But before that, do you have a pen handy?
Give me one and hurry up.
Alright, listen up.
I swear I'm not joking when I ask this.
Do you think I could have
written these words by myself,
on my own body, without help?
Mm-hmm.
By any chance, Wes,
have I been asking you the same
few questions over and over again?
Do me a favor.
About those questions I keep asking you,
would you mind answering them for me again?
I
don't
know.
To the female wing as
of two days ago for real
i've been back here for
two days yeah and i hope
you feel better soon
you'll need it two days i
was asking the same
questions for two damn days
but why would i defeat
the stand user her name is
mew mew wait holy crap
could it be no no way it's a
stand attack to prevent me
from breaking out of this
hellhole and i'm being
attacked right this moment
everything up to emporio's visit
but after that um
after that after that i i'm sure i
must have i think something happened
Oh no, there's more of this shit?
What is all this?
Incidentally, Gwess, you know
someone who goes by the name Mew Mew?
Leaky there, Jolene, you
can ask new questions.
Yeah, she's from the floor above.
If I'm right, she's a bleach
blonde, bad split ends.
About your height, I'd say.
I don't know what shit she pulled to
get locked up, but I bet it was major.
At any rate, the woman's trash.
Got it.
Where can I go find her now?
If you'd been looking,
you would have seen her.
She just walked past
the door a second ago.
Gwess, tell me one more time.
What'd she look like?
I'd say her height's around
five foot seven and change.
Blonde hair, bitchy
stare, wicked split ends.
Where's cut out stockings?
Wait, I'm back here?
How did I end up back at
the female ward again?
Who is Miu Miu? Is she...
Is there a problem, Han?
No.
You said you were going
to go eat just now.
It's almost time for lunch.
Good timing.
Oh, is that so?
Don't you dare think about
escaping Jolene Kujo.
I don't care what your plan is.
You and your friends will never be
able to get past Jailhouse Lock or me.
Halesnake's true identity was
the priest, Father Poochie.
F .F.
pinned it down for us.
And?
Then they're gone, huh?
Drink up. You've earned it.
We'll avenge you.
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?
Meal ticket now!
What are you talking about?
I'm here to get some lunch.
Then you better show me your lunch ticket.
You're walking out of here hungry
if you try to pull any shit.
Hurry up, show me.
Don't have all day.
Why don't you just step aside?
Bye. Get out of here.
Next.
Shit, did I forget it
on my bed in the cell?
I'd better find a place to write it down.
What was I doing just now?
I know I came back to
the cell for something.
What was it?
Come on, think.
It had to be at least important
enough to take the trouble.
Jolyne!
That's my lunch you're eating!
Drop that fork now!
Oh man, it's almost gone!
That was my favorite cheese
penne and you snarfed it all!
Dumbass!
You put your own meal ticket
in your pocket this morning!
Sorry.
I'll use this to go get you
a replacement meal then.
It's fine really, don't.
How about you just give me your meal
ticket and I'll go get it myself.
Thank you.
And maybe you should write
it down somewhere this time.
I gave my meal ticket to Guaz,
I didn't lose it. My bad.
Who's this? A user?
That can only mean that it's a stand.
Oh, that's right.
I have to go find Emporio.
I was trying to escape
from the isolated cell.
And I was probably with
Emporio at the time.
That's the only explanation.
I bet he knows something
about it that can help me.
He knows I want to escape.
Hey, we have a big problem.
There's no more mustard in here.
It's empty!
How about a new one?
This again?
Do they serve the same
crap every day here?
I'm not even all that hungry.
I'll just eat the cheese
penny, that's good.
Hey Jolene, mind if I sit down?
I'll take that as a yes.
I stepped on a fucking cockroach earlier.
Now there's dead bug on my shoes
Who is this woman so weird?
She obviously knows who I am tall
blonde split ends cut out stockings
You asshole?
The hell are you doing to my lunch?
This needs some mustard!
Maybe a little ketchup to?
Dressing would be the perfect touch!
That's delicious!
Thanks a lot!
You look so familiar! What's your name?
Oh no!
I'm so sorry! Jolene!
Look what a mess I've made!
Please let me clean it up!
Oh!
It got all over your arm too!
It's really dirty!
I'm just gonna wipe away all that grunge!
Scrubby!
Scrub!
There we go! All cleaned! Stand up!
Isn't that better now?
Let me see inside that pocket, too.
I'll just leave that for you to look over.
Jailhouse lock.
Anyone who, while trying to escape,
touches the bars my stands in will only be
able to remember three things at a time,
sadly.
A life of threes appears simple,
but it's actually more difficult
than losing all of your memories.
You will continuously repeat,
experience, and be painfully reminded
that everything you do is useless.
An arduous feedback loop that
slowly erodes your spirit.
Eventually, it'll even
drain your will to escape.
It might feel something like paralysis,
but really, that's your appropriate
punishment for trying to break out of prison.
I know I need something, but what?
What's important?
What's something I cannot forget?
What do I need to break
through this situation?
Just one thing!
That's all I need!
I gotta remember it.
Cause if I can't do that
now, I'll forget it forever!
One goddamn thing.
But what matters most is...
This, this is all I need.
I'll leave room for one more.
Now it's down to these two.
These two are the only ones I need.
I can 86 the rest myself.
And get back to my goal of
breaking the fuck out of here!
I...
I spilled my water!
This is really bad!
I'm being electrocuted.
I have to pull the plug before I die.
Otherwise, I...
I can't leave this room through that exit
and meet Jolene like I'm supposed to.
I have something important to tell
Jolene. I gotta go. She needs me.
No matter what happens,
I can't forget that.
I have to get out of this room quickly.
Oh, no.
I spilled my water.
I have to pull the plug before I die.
I'm being electrocuted.
Otherwise, I can't leave this room
through that exit and meet Jolene.
I won't be able to see her.
Wait a minute.
I have to go see Emporio?
I remember seeing something like that on
Jolene's arm right before I wiped it off.
I suppose I'll have to confirm it, though.
Still, no one's escaping from here.
it's an airtight fortress.
My head is filled with hope.
Of some place other than here.
Although you think I smile.
Inside and all the while.
I'm wondering about my destiny.
I'm thinking
about all
the things I'd like to do?
In my life,
I'm a dreamer,
a distant dreamer,
dreaming far
away from today.
Thank you.